<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meteor Observation Notebook</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notebook">NotebookActivity</string>
    <string name="begin_observation">Begin Observation</string>
    <string name="petnica_meteor_group">Petnica Meteor Group</string>
    <string name="meteor_observation_notebook">Meteor Observation Notebook</string>
    <string name="observation_results">Observation Results</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="test_notebook">Test Notebook</string>
    <string name="empty">Empty</string>
    <string name="nights">Nights</string>
    <string name="instructions_text">
        Begin observation:\n
        \n
        During this activity, you\'ll be writing down your observations. The screen
        is black so as not to distract and drain battery. When you want to write something
        down (meteor, cloudiness, etc), click Volume Down button to enable the notebook, which
        lets you write anything down with your finger(s) on the screen.To confirm the writing,
        click Volume Up which will disable the notebook and save whatever you wrote. Both of
        these actions are confirmed by a short vibration. Volume Down can also be used to erase
        the notebook if you made a mistake, and Volume Up to turn it off. While the notebook
        is disabled (default state), you can\'t draw anything on the screen. The default buttons
        for leaving the activity - Recent Apps, Home, Back and Lock are all disabled during
        observation to prevent accidental leave. To finish the observation, hold down Recent Apps
        and Back buttons.\n
        \n
        Observation results:\n
        \n
        After you\'ve finished observing, you can find everything you\'ve written
        in this section, divided into nights. Swipe the screen to scroll through your notes.\n
        \n
        Test notebook:\n
        \n
        A simulation of an observation notebook, where you can see what you\'re writing.
        Everything you write here is discarded and is used for testing only.
    </string>
</resources>
